{
    "id": "5dbddefd660f48e797d3e72b7e07d7da",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I have engaged a private tutor ................................. me English.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to teach",
                "for teaching"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ca614a73de7b4d10aba773f787d9e781"
        },
        {
            "question": "The woman was .................................. mean to be popular.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "too"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d34ef9f11b134fb1b92cf5da574ac367"
        },
        {
            "question": "I looked out of the window .................................... the green pastures.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for seeing",
                "to see"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6c055a00c6ee44d7b852f70ef021c57e"
        },
        {
            "question": "The proposal is ...................................... unreasonable to be accepted.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "so",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "29e5263a3b7843aab4cbfac5583bda26"
        },
        {
            "question": "Our country expects every man ................................. his duty.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to do",
                "doing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "57186fde5a82471bbddd58eb85f2fd91"
        },
        {
            "question": "My mother was very much delighted ................................... about my fatherâ€™s safe arrival.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to hear",
                "to hearing",
                "hearing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2c36d615fba1451d8430630d19d1a221"
        },
        {
            "question": "He works hard ........................................ the first rank.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to win",
                "for winning"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6f6b3d0fdf754e45bda33a82bc3ee9b5"
        },
        {
            "question": "He went to the USA ........................................ higher education.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to pursue",
                "for pursuing",
                "to pursuing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "87d960e082954878b43af1070d46989b"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is .................................... weak to walk without help.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "too",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cc66cd99f39742ff8878801dc396704d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The tea is ..................................... hot for me to drink.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "so",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dd03af9687904ce1af6261a9553f55e3"
        }
    ]
}